can't even have a recipe go to pioneer woman i know garnon like i'm giving you like there's recipe like there's cookbooks like figure it out figure it out so i'm very interested to see what that's gonna look like yeah it's it's
I was just wondering from your side of things.
Yeah.
You just can't use it in the history field.
I think a lot of profs are doing either Canvas lockdown browser, but there's still ways you can cheat with it.
I think a lot of it's going to be blue books and just written out, which I'm okay.
I think that's great.
That's more what grad school looks like if you're interested in that.
And it's better honing in communication skills, writing skills, and critical thinking skills.
And those are all core missions of a lot of the history classes at A&M.
So yeah, I think it's perfect.
Can you tell whatever you read it?
Okay.
Because I write how I talk.
so that's really like yeah accessible yeah you're uh yeah so like if you use 15 commas and it's a single sentence i just know that's how you talk that's great i'll tell you a couple periods where you don't you know what i mean but if it's um i i use end dashes and i use all three commas i have
Like, I'm an M dash truther.
Like, don't take that from me.
So, again, if it's a kid that is doing a weirdly okay job, then I'll kind of be like, mmm.
Again, it's still early in the semester.
We'll see.
I think handwriting is also a big thing.
If you have chicken scratch, then I'm going to say you don't probably write a lot yourself.
Because I write everything out a lot before I type it up.
But...
It's just a mindset I don't know a lot about, but you can 100% tell.
You can 100% tell.
It's interesting to me who can and cannot tell because there's very much a generational gap to who can and cannot tell.
Especially with generative AI.
Like pictures, that's weird when people can't tell.
It's getting so...
I've actually got...
trick for the very first time i was like wow this is getting really good no it's getting really really good yeah i think in the next five years there'll be a full thing like made by humans or not using generative ai i do think that would be that like um i think in that first episode of vince gilligan's new show blurberus have you seen it on apple tv
the end credit said like made a hundred percent by humans.
Awesome.
Yeah.
So like, that's going to be like, I think it's going to be a thing.
I think that marketing campaigns are, I think it's going to become a sense of artisanal mate handcrafted by humans.
I think that's good.
It's the newer.
I a hundred percent.
It's going to be the new organic.
Yeah.
I think you just have to shift it and market it of like, this is human made human mind.
I think.
Yeah.
I think it's good.
It's going to be, yeah.
Higher luxury.
If real people made it, I think that,
You're right.
That does have a lot to do with consumerism and production.
You tell someone the water impact of it and they think nothing of it.
You're telling Californians to take 15 minute showers and then building a data center that uses the water in a day so someone can tell them make a schedule for me today.
Make this email.
Make this picture of me.
Yeah.
And so I think also just everyday life I don't
If someone shows me something AI, I go, ew.
I'll be rude.
Like, I don't care.
It's stopping it on the local, personal level and saying, gross.
You use AI?
I don't, like, I will be 100% mean about that.
I don't care.
Yeah, shame them.
Shame them.
If anything, shame people.
Yes.
So, again, is this different when it comes to math or science?
I'm sure.
But all humanity, this side of campus, we have no business.
We have no business doing that.
No.
Yeah, that's why I was very, like, hackles raised when they told us to.
Yeah.
No, I completely get that.
No, it's.
Yeah.
Mm-mm.
No, but I think, you know, people, students are always happy to be here.
You can feel that on campus.
They want to be here.
They are excited.
I think that's wonderful.
So.
What are some, like, say that this whole place closed down tomorrow.
What are some of the memories that will stick with you?
going forward that you tell your family?
Yeah, probably my training.
Just that would take, you know, in a new professional career shift, I'd take that with me, obviously.
But Megan and I got the giggles the other day.
There's a video of Michael Jackson.
He's, like, promoting a tour.
And he goes, like, I hate touring.
I go through hell touring.
And they go, like, Michael, like, do one, like, do positive.
And so they cut.
He goes, I love to tour.
I just kept going like, I don't know.
We just kept doing it and it really got me.
For some reason, the song Mary Did You Know got brought up so it was like, Mary did you tour?
It was connecting and it was just so funny.
But yeah, I'd say probably most of my memories with Megan and that's probably my biggest thing.
What I do share with family is more like my personal stripes, highs and lows than maybe the more academic side of things.
Yeah.
That's really nice.
I love to turn.
I have some legacy questions.
Yes.
So Haskell Monroe, and he's one of the people that did, like, hundreds of interviews that we have.
And he has a list of his questions from Wilde.
Okay.
But some of them that I think I should continue on in the legacy is...
Um, this one, if you were a consultant to aid in leadership today, what advice you would give them?
This is a question from him from the seventies.
Um, I'd say fire board of regents and have them be educators.
I'm not saying just, I could like, I don't need PhDs in there.
Right.
I can have high school teachers, elementary school teachers that are interested in administrative work.
As long as you have an educator background, that's who should be making decisions for this campus and the system as a whole.
I'd say stop buying up these small schools.
We don't need the system to be bigger.
I think it's attractive, obviously.
Focus on what's going on here.
Let's look at what are our food options on campus?
Conjoined are our food options on campus.
You can only go to like the Aggie Express little like almost gas station pretty much here.
But engineering buildings have Starbucks in the engineering buildings.
How are we showing favoritism to certain majors and colleges?
And I understand it's money and enrollment numbers.
I do.
I get that.
But how do we make those other departments equally as attractive?
Because it will draw more people in.
It will draw more people in.
You know, ask yourself, what do you want to be known as?
Just an ag or just an engineering school?
When if you're an R1 university, every department's impacted in that.
And that is evident.
And we just had a Pulitzer Prize winner, Caleb McDaniel.
He got his master's here.
Wild.
Yes.
So, what else?
What?
Was he English?
History.
Yeah.
Yeah, he works at Rice.
He was just here.
Yeah.
I got you.
Yes.
No, please.
Yeah.
Probably that in the nicest way possible.
Just I'd lean towards ags teaching, raising ags and making decisions for ags.
Yeah.
Just if example, like they dissolved the faculty Senate.
That's who could have been reviewing syllabi.
But you're overworking your department heads.
So there's just a disconnect.
This also is another one that he would always ask is that if you were given a million dollars and you had to give it to some part of this university, what would you invest in it?
What needs it involved you?
Hmm.
Probably the library.
Probably some of it.
The small animal hospital.
I worked there for a little bit.
Um, and they do so much.
There's an actual also vet people go to.
Oh my gosh.
George Strait goes there for his animals.
Like it's just, it serves the community as well.
Um, probably a little more transportation.
Um, some of those buses are a little old.
Yeah.
Um,
Yeah, I'd probably say that.
I think that's a good movie.
Yeah.
I hope.
I've heard everything from all to football to... Yeah.
They're good.
I've heard everything from... Yeah.
Yeah.
A million dollars to the football is like $10,000.
Like, comparatively, like, that's how much it is.
They're okay.
Yeah, they're okay.
I promise you they're okay.
Yeah.
Um...
Is there any topics that you really did want to talk about that I just didn't touch on?
I don't think so.
I can't be touched.
And then my last one is, what are the feelings that you hold in your heart for Texas A&M?
Right now, if you asked me that two weeks ago, I might have changed.
Appreciation, you know, gave me my husband, gave me my education.
Frustration right now.
Defensiveness.
I'm very defensive of A&M.
There's the, you know, whenever it's UT rivalry week, it's like, who didn't get into UT goes to A&M?
No, I never applied to UT.
I never wanted to be in Austin.
Like, I chose here.
Yeah, just love, defensiveness, and frustration, I think, probably right now.
Yeah.
I think it's because of the love.
It's because of the love so much, it's breaking your heart.
You know what it can be, so, and what it is.
Yeah, because if you didn't care about it, then you wouldn't.
Yeah.
Yeah, if this really is just a place you're getting a piece of paper, who cares?
But I have every intention to have a long relationship with Anna, so, yeah.
I think that's what makes this place actually special.
The amount of alumni who come.
We're such an engaged alumni.
Truly.
Like rivals the nation.
Really, truly.
So I think that's so special.
So pissing off half of the alumni is probably not a good decision.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Of course.